[
  {
    "Question": "Hallo Ivan.",
    "Answer": [ "Bok Ivane." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Hallo Ivan.",
    "Answer": [ "Bok Ivane." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Morgen.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobro jutro." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Morgen Klara.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobro jutro Klara." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Tag.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobar dan." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Tag Julia.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobar dan Julia." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Guten Abend.",
    "Answer": [ "Dobra večer." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Gute Nacht.",
    "Answer": [ "Laku noć." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Auf Wiedersehen.",
    "Answer": [ "Doviđenja." ]
  },
  {
    "Question": "Tschüss.",
    "Answer": [ "Bok." ]
  }
]